And secondly, medicines will give benefit messages
in this, as long as there will be a buying opportunity from the top down of this ship,
victory will be created because that is
why on the call of things, here you like
share, so wait 212, so Ranjit Singh
is on for the bank and I will move slowly anyway,
first you will see pregnancy 40 percent people because
but and strong that I am later, so
thought leadership has been appointed, the
market will move only through policy, the bank will
pull towards the stage, not towards weakness,
taking the relationship downwards, so even if the difficulty of the bank is
more mentioned to you, but 21
thousand 314 friends, there is a congestion zone, I
was at the bank, I will not give advice to buy here, but if
we do it again on Monday, it will fall short, it is
selfless, there is a lot of bullishness in the person, the question should
come and topless, we 20800
simple and fix a date for the temple,
friends, note down these levels, things
are welcome, as you all are, so that you
start staying picky for the same reason, Aniket, the picture is great, fun,
your face must be glowing too, what better to
do, hate  This company
is a big company of India, the company is doing and it will
soon come
obscene and will show, advised Ajay to buy on loot system,
o clock 135 and if you want to put it, you can
buy temple jewellery, this is for you, we will
take it from here, now the second Chauth fast,
friends, glasses, the second question is absolutely a
very great company, by the name of the company, it is the
biggest private company of India in the market, it is
very good, this
company's business is that Meghnad should
buy, I come back to you at
1250, your mixture target, this is a
long March,
after buying, but get very excited and
send a message that an obscene is going to come for you, you have done
futures trading, it will come,
wait a little, the Teli community will give it to the Teli community,
just for a minute, I will put it in the media, the
chart is for the hips, Kunal, this is for the zodiac sign